{
    "questions": [
        {
            "category": "house",
            "type": "not asked",
            "question": "Where will you live?\n",
            "answers": [
                "Mansion",
                "Apartment",
                "Shack",
                "House"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "salary",
            "type": "spinner",
            "question": "Money can't buy you hapiness, but it can buy a lot of other things...\n",
            "answers": [
                    "$10,000",
                    "$15,000",
                    "$25,000",
                    "$35,000",
                    "$50,000",
                    "$75,000",
                    "$100,000",
                    "$1,000,000"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "kids",
            "type": "spinner",
            "question": "Kids are the future...are they in yours...\n",
            "answers": [
                "Twins, their names are Cindy and Mindy, they might be plotting aginst you...",
                "Only child, you're more like their best friend than their parent",
                "A boy and a girl, you've called them by their first initial so much you can't remeber their actual names",
                "10 kids, you should see the grocery list!",
                "0, your time is your own"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "transportation",
            "type": "switch",
            "question": "How did you get to school when you were little?\n",
            "answers": {
                "Big yellow school bus": "Your cousin's old Honda, but it's got an aftermarket spoiler, so it's pretty sweet.",
                "Rode your bike": "A Harly Davidson, you would rather die than be a cager!",
                "Backseat of your mom's minivan": "Subaru Forester, the safety record is simply impeccable.",
                "Walked...uphill..both ways...in the snow": "Ford F-150. Haul stuff? No. But you could if you needed to!"
            }
        },
        {
            "category": "transportation",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What was your dream car as a teenager?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", dreams really do come true!"
        },
        {
            "category": "transportation",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What was your first car?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", maybe you can tell people it's an antique."
            
        },
        {
            "category": "transportation",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "Name a type of public transportation:\n",
            "answers": 
                ", if you put in headphones and breathe through your mouth, it's not so bad."
        },
        {
            "category": "transportation",
            "type": "switch",
            "question": "How do you get to work?\n",
            "answers": {
                "Walk, when the weather allows for it": "An E-bike, its great for getting around town...unless a tourist takes it thinking its part of the city bike share.",
                "Drive, obviously": "A luxury sedan, but it has sport mode for when you feel spunky",
                "Bike, you also recycle in case anyone was wondering": "The fixie you built from spare parts during your volunteer hours at the community Gear Hub",
                "Public transportation, putting your tax dollars to work": "In the age of Uber, who needs a car!"
            }
        },
        {
            "category": "career",
            "type": "switch",
            "question": "How do you unwind at home?\n",
            "answers": {
                "Watch TV": "Showbiz, baby! Small screens, big screens you're on them all!",
                "Tidying up": "Watch out Marie Kondo, you're sparking joy all around you, while building your organization empire!",
                "Cooking and baking": "You left the corporate world to enter the wild west of restauranteuring, how hard could it be?",
                "Crafting": "Right now, you're between jobs... you're focusing your efforts more on manifesting rather than actively looking."
            }
        },
        {
            "category": "career",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What is your current job?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", you've always considered yourself a company man."
        },
        {
            "category": "career",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What did you want to be when you grew up?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", if only those bullies in middle school could see you now!"
        },
        {
            "category": "career",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What was the worst job you've ever had?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", you're just a hamster stuck on the wheel of life."
        },
        {
            "category": "location",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What city and state where you born in?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", born and raised."
        },
        {
            "category": "location",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "Where was your favorite vacation?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", just another day in paradise!"
        },
        {
            "category": "location",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "Name a state and capital:\n",
            "answers": 
                ", you like to be close to the power."
        },
        {
            "category": "location",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "Where was the last place you lived?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", how did you wind up back here!?!"
        },
        {
            "category": "location",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "If you could travel anywhere, where would you go?\n",
            "answers":
                ", not a bad place to call home."
        },
        {
            "category": "partner",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "Who is your celebrity crush?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", you're always red carpet ready."
        },
        {
            "category": "partner",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "Who did you think was a dreamboat in middle school?\n",
            "answers":
                ", it was always meant to be!"
        },
        {
            "category": "partner",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "Who was your least favorite teacher?\n",
            "answers":
                ", gross!"
        },
        {
            "category": "partner",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "Name a politician:\n",
            "answers":
                ", you always were drawn to power."
        },
        {
            "category": "partner",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What is your next door neighbor's name?\n",
            "answers": 
                ", sometimes love is right around the corner."
        },
        {
            "category": "pet",
            "type": "switch",
            "question": "Which do you find the creepiest?\n",
            "answers": {
                "Tarantula": "A tarantula, it only got out a couple of times.",
                "Oppossum": "an oppossum, if you squint it's kind of cute.",
                "Hissing Cockroach": "a hissing cockroach, they're just misunderstood.",
                "Centipede": "a centipede, it was in your shower one day and the rest is history!"
            }
        },
        {
            "category": "pet",
            "type": "switch",
            "question": "Which do you think is the smartest?\n",
            "answers": {
                "Robot": "A robot, you've programmed it to bring you toilet paper when you run out.",
                "Golden Retriever": "a golden retriever, you have matching outfits.",
                "Potbelly Pig": "potbelly pig, when you bought it, the lady said it would stay small!",
                "Octopus": "an octopus, it's unclear who is whose pet at this point."
            }
        },
        {
            "category": "pet",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What animal do you think is the cutest?\n",
            "answers":
                ", all other pets pale in comparison!"
        },
        {
            "category": "pet",
            "type": "field",
            "question": "What type of pet did you have growing up?\n",
            "answers":
                ", it's a classic."
        }
    ]
}